Guide to the General Frederick Steele Papers, 1845-1965 (inclusive), 1862-1868 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series IA. Correspondence and papers of General Frederick Steele, 1845-1890.
  - Correspondence 1864, July 10-20. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 25. 1864, July 19.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 53. Classification--hospital stewards.
    - 26. 1864, July 19.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 232. Printed. Lincoln proclamation calling for 500,000 volunteers.
    - 27. 1864, July 19.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 233. Proclamation--suspend writ of habeas corpus and establish martial law in Kentucky.
    - 28-30. 1864, July 20.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 54. 2 ADfs by [FS] and printed. Death of S. A. Rice.
    - 31. 1864, July 20.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 55. Printed, s. John F. Lacey. Re: Lt. Mackenzie.
    - 32. 1864, July 20.Division of West Mississippi. Printed circular No. 5, s. B. F. Morey. Communications for Headquarters.
  - Correspondence 1864, July 21-31. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 1. 1864, July 21.[FS] to A. Lincoln. [ADf?]. Recommends promotion of Col. Clayton.
    - 2. 1864, July 22.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 23. Printed. Re: J. J. Reynolds.
    - 3. 1864, July 22.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 24. Printed. General court martial--Jos. Goodsell.
    - 4. 1864, July 22.C. A. Henry to FS. ALS. Procuring horses, etc., personal, Arkansas campaign.
    - 5. 1864, July 22.C. A. Henry to FS. ALS. Problem of transporting horses.
    - 6. 1864, July 22.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy certified by W. D. Green. Enemy movements.
    - 7. 1864, July 23.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 56. Printed. Rations.
    - 8. 1864, July 23.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 25. Printed. Re: allowable resignations of medical officers.
    - 9. 1864, July 23.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 26. Printed. Abolishes Brigade Acting Inspector General Offices.
    - 10. 1864, July 24.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy certified by W. D. Green. Shelby's movements.
    - 11. 1864, July 25.Division of the Mississippi. G.O. No. 21. Printed, s. L. Carper. Prohibition on export of some agricultural products from Tennessee and use of grain for distilling.
    - 12. 1864, July 25.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 27. Printed. W. H. Wood, Provost Marshall General of Division.
    - 13. [1864?], July 25.Harriet F. Green to FS. ALS. Appeal.
    - 14. 1864, July 25.[FS] to Geo. H. Gordon. [ADf]. Suggests procedure at St. Charles.
    - 15. 1864, July 25.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 234. Printed. Crook and Emory.
    - 16. 1864, July 26.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy certified by W. D. Green. Bribery, Davidson's hostility.
    - 17. 1864, July 26.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 235. Printed. Re-enlistments.
    - 18. 1864, July 27.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 57. Printed. Military commission.
    - 19. 1864, July 27.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 28. Printed. Leaves of absence, resignations, furloughs.
    - 20. 1864, July 27.Division of West Mississippi - Office Medical Inspector and Chief Medical Officer. Printed circular No. 1. Titles.
    - 21. 1864, July 27.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 58. Re-enlistments, musters-out.
    - 22. 1864, July 28.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 29. Re: consolidation Corps d' Afrique.
    - 23. [1864], July 28.Sallie McPhesters to FS. ALS. Thanks.
    - 24. 1864, July 28.Sam. D. Tompkins to FS. ALS. Gratitude.
    - 25. 1864, July 28.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 236. Printed. Re: W. F. Smith, E. O. C. Ord, J. H. Martindale, D. B. Birney, A. H. Terry.
    - 26. 1864, July 28.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 237. Printed. Re: Wallace, Hunter, Wright.
    - 27. 1864, July 29.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 58. Printed. General court martial.
    - 28. 1864, July 29.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 30. Printed. Rations.
    - 29. 1864, July 29.Division of West Mississippi - Office Assistant Inspector General. Printed circular No. 3. Reports.
    - 30. 1864, July 29.Sue M. Manter to FS. ALS. Re: Col. Manter's death, family's grief.
    - 31. 1864, July 29.[FS] to E. R. S. Canby. Copy, fragment. Enemy activity, location.
    - 32. 1864, July 30.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 31. Printed. Militia--compulsory military service.
    - 33. 1864, July 30.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 238. Printed. O. O. Howard, H. W. Slocum, D. S. Stanley.
    - 34. 1864, July 31.District of Eastern Arkansas. G.O. No. 47. Printed, s. W. Chandler. Mourning
  - Correspondence 1864, August 1-7. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 1. 1864, Aug. 1.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy certified by W. D. Green. Reports skirmish near Big Creek, Shelby' force.
    - 2. 1964, Aug. 1.[FS] to C. C. Washburn. ADf. Requests cooperation.
    - 3. 1864, Aug. 1.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 59. Changes of mustering officers.
    - 4. 1864, Aug. 2.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 32. Printed. Discharges.
    - 5. 1864, Aug. 2.M. D. London (N. Y. Tribune) to FS. ALS. Helena threatened, local destruction, asks aid.
    - 6. 1864, Aug. 2.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 61. Re: new commissions and term of service in volunteers.
    - 7. 1864, Aug. 3.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 59. Printed. Aug. 4--day of humiliation and prayer.
    - 8. 1864, Aug. 3.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 33. Printed Trade and intercourse with or in rebel States.
    - 9. 1864, Aug. 4.Anna Laing to FS. ALS. Asks leave of absence for fiance.
    - 10. 1864, Aug. 5.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 239. Printed. Reprimand Lt. L. M. Gardner.
    - 11. 1864, Aug. 6.P. St. George Cooke to FS. ALS. Gen. McClellan adopted his cavalry tactics
    - 12. 1864, Aug. 7.[FS] to C. C. Washburn. ADf. Gen. West after McRea and Shelby, Washburn's seizure of FS's horses and troops at Memphis.
    - 13. 1864, Aug. 7.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 240. Printed. Middle Military Division, Sheridan.
  - Correspondence 1864, August 8-19. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 1. 1864, Aug. 8.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 60. Printed. General court martial.
    - 2. 1864, Aug. 8.[FS] to E. R. S. Canby. Copy certified by W. D. Green. Reports on move against enemy, Dobbins at Helena.
    - 3. 1864, Aug. 8.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 242. Printed. Amnesty to insurgent enemies.
    - 4. 1864, Aug. 9.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 34. Printed. Accounting for public monies from sale of seized property, etc.
    - 5. 1864, Aug. 9.W. Myers to FS. ALS. Staff personal differences (Carr and Henry), Missouri guerrillas.
    - 6. 1864, Aug. 9.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 241. Printed. Re: J. C. Davis. [possibly misdated].
    - 7. 1864, Aug. 9.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 243. Printed. Muster of recruits for new organizations.
    - 8. 1864, Aug. 10.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 35. Printed. Officers dismissed.
    - 9. 1864, Aug. 11.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 61. Printed. s. W. D. Green. Court martial.
    - 10. 1864, Aug. 11.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 36. Printed, s. John F. S. Gray. Headquarters of 19th Army Corps at New Orleans.
    - 11. 1864, Aug. 12.Division of the Mississippi. G.O. No. 22. Printed. Rebel deserters and refugees.
    - 12. 1864, Aug. 12.Sarah Palmer to FS. ALS. Sends punch bowl and glasses.
    - 13. 1864, Aug. 12.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 244. Printed. Transportation of school books for Freedmen.
    - 14. 1864, Aug. 12.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 245. Printed. An act to provide for efficiency of Navy.
    - 15. 1864, Aug. 13.[B. O. Carr] to Lewis B. Parsons. True copy s. C. A. Henry. Re: scarcity of forage, transportation. On verso: copies of referral by Parsons 8/24/64, Parsons to Carr 8/25/64.
    - 16. 1864, Aug. 13.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 246. Printed. Rules and regulations for preventing collisions on the water.
    - 17-18. 1864, Aug. 14.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 37. 2 copies, one s. A. S. Montgomery. Officers to move with troops.
    - 19. 1864, Aug. 14.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy certified by W. D. Green. West's victory at Searcy, move against Shelby.
    - 20. 1864, Aug. 15.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 62. Printed. Re-enlistments and bounties.
    - 21. 1864, Aug. 15.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 295. [of 1863]. Soldiers from Minnesota allowed to vote in State elections. Stamp of E. D. Townsend.
    - 22. 1864, Aug. 16.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 63. Printed. Enroll and organize local militia.
    - 23. 1864, Aug. 17.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 64. Printed. J. Jaehne dishonorably dismissed.
    - 24. 1864, Aug. 18.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 64. Necessary papers for transfers.
    - 25. 1864, Aug. 18.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 65. Veteran Reserve Corps.
    - 26. 1864, Aug. 19.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 38. Printed. An act to establish a uniform systems of ambulances in armies of U.S.
  - Correspondence 1864, August 20-31. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 1. 1864, Aug. 20.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 65. Printed. West, chief of cavalry for Dept.
    - 2. 1864, Aug. 20.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 39. Printed. Holding correspondence with or giving intelligence to enemy directly or indirectly punishable by death. Cook of the N. Y. Herald and Chadwick of N. Y. Tribune.
    - 3. 1864, Aug. 20.J. Young Scammons to FS. ALS. Enquires as to the conduct of his son, worried about liquor.
    - 4. 1864, Aug. 20.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy certified by W. D. Green. Rebels moving toward Little Rock, Magruder superceded Price, to hold Pine Bluff.
    - 5. 1864, Aug. 20.[FS] to Richard Yates. ADf. Requests another company for pontoon battalion and that Max Webber command the battalion.
    - 6. 1864, Aug. 21.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 40. Printed. Discontinue U.S. General Hospital at Natchez.
    - 7. 1864, Aug. 22.Division of the Mississippi. G.O. No. 28. Printed. R. W. Johnson, chief of cavalry of Division.
    - 8. 1864, Aug. 22.War Department - A.G.O. S.O. No. 452. Contemporary holograph copy, extract. L. Rhoades Honorably mustered out. s. C. H. Whittelsey.
    - 9. 1864, Aug. 24.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 66. Printed. General court martial.
    - 10. 1864, Aug. 25.T. D. Seawell to FS. ALS. Wishes to be recommended as an officer.
    - 11. 1864, Aug. 25.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 247. Printed. Uniform for chaplains.
    - 12. 1864, Aug. 26.Division of the Mississippi. G.O. No. 24. Printed. Eastern, Chief Quarter Master of Division.
    - 13. 1864, Aug. 26.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 41. Printed. Rations for civilian employees.
    - 14. 1864, Aug. 26.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy certified by W. D. Green. Rebel attack on Railroad, Devall's Bluff presumed next, Price reported planning a raid against Missouri.
    - 15. 1864, Aug. 26.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 68. Enlistment bounties.
    - 16. 1864, Aug. 27.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 67. Printed. Military commission.
    - 17. 1864, Aug. 27.C. A. Henry to FS. ALS. Shipping forage.
    - 18. 1864, Aug. 28.Armies of the United States. S.O. No. 82. Printed. Confederate deserters.
    - 19. 1864, Aug. 29.Division of the Mississippi. G.O. No. 25. Printed, s. C. [S.?] Newlin. Trade with States in insurrection.
    - 20. 1864, Aug. 29.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 42. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Amnesty to insurgent enemies.
    - 21. 1864, Aug. 29.Lewis Merrill. to[FS]. ALS. Quelling a rumor re: reasons for removal of his regiment, Etc., thinks McClellan will be nominated at Chicago.
    - 22. 1864, Aug. 30.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 248. Printed. Hunter replaced by Crook, Dept. of West Virginia.
    - 23. 1864, Aug. 30.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 249. Printed. E. S. Parker, private secretary on Grant's staff
    - 24. 1864, Aug. 31.Division of W. Mississippi. Printed circular No. 6. Captured maps or drawings of Mobile Bay.
    - 25. 1864, Aug. 31.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 43. Gaster court martial.
    - 26. 1864, Aug. 31.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 250. Printed. Rolls of prisoners of war.
    - 27. 1864, Aug. 31.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 251. Printed. Courts martial for separate Brigades.
    - 28. 1864, Aug. 31.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 252. Printed. Exams for Quarter Master officers, etc.
  - Correspondence 1864, September 1-9. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 1. 1864, Sept. 1.T. M. Jacks. Aphorisms on Government. Printed broadside.
    - 2. 1864, Sept. 1.R. R. Livingston to [FS]. ALS. Re: Indian raid in North Dakota.
    - 3. 1864, Sept. 1.[?] M_____ to [FS]. ALS. Railroad, McClellan's nomination.
    - 4. 1864, Sept. 1.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Tel., copy. Shelby's movements.
    - 5. 1864, Sept. 1.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 71. Authorized Commissaries and Assistant Commissaries of Musters.
    - 6. 1864, Sept. 3.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 44. Printed. Rations.
    - 7. 1864, Sept. 3.R. B. Marcy to FS. ALS. McClellan's nomination at Democratic convention, Sherman's capture of Atlanta.
    - 8. 1864, Sept. 5.G. L. Miller to [FS]. ALS. Pro McClellan, Presidential campaign, Wheeler at Jenkins Ferry.
    - 9. 1864, Sept. 6.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 45. Printed. Authority for granting furloughs and discharges.
    - 10. 1864, Sept. 6.J. W. Grimes to [FS]. ALS. Fails to secure appointment for Capt. Joy.
    - 11. 1864, Sept. 6.FS to C. C. Andrews. Tel., copy s. W. D. Green. Col. Stoneman, Napier beat Witt.
    - 12. 1864, Sept. 6.FS to O. O. Washburn. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Rebel movements, plan attack on Little Rock, asks aid.
    - 13. 1864, Sept. 6.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 72. Terms of re-enlistment.
    - 14. 1864, Sept. 6.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 73. Mustering out of officers.
    - 15. 1864, Sept. 7.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Reinforcements, to take field against Shelby and Fagan.
    - 16. 1864, Sept. 8.G. B. McClellan. Letter of Acceptance. Printed broadside.
    - 17. 1864, Sept. 9.E. D. Chapman to C. A. Henry. Copy s. C. A. Henry. Forage requisition.
    - 18. 1864, Sept. 9.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 46. Printed. Speedy punishment of guerrillas.
    - 19. 1864, Sept. 9.C. A. Henry to E. D. Chapman. [ALS?]. Forage requisitions.
    - 20. 1864, Sept. 9.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Lewisburg skirmish, parole of prisoners.
  - Correspondence 1864, September 10-20. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1. 1864, Sept. 10.C. A. Henry to FS. ALS. Deficiency of forage.
    - 2. 1864, Sept. 10.FS to Wm. S. Rosecrans. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Price heading for Missouri.
    - 3 1864, Sept. 10.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 253. Printed. Retirement of Gen. George D. Ramsay.
    - 4. 1864, Sept. 12.Dept. of Arkansas. Printed circular. Requests report of those on detached service.
    - 5. 1864, Sept. 12.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 47. Printed. Staff of Major General commanding.
    - 6. 1864, Sept. 12.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy s. W. D. Green. Enemy strength at Monticello, etc.
    - 7. 1864, Sept. 12.FS to J. A. Mower. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Instructions to operate against Price and Shelby.
    - 8. 1864, Sept. 12.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 254. Printed. Deserters.
    - 9. 1864, Sept. 12.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 255. Printed. Exchanged prisoners.
    - 10. 1864, Sept. 13.J. A. Newberry to FS. ALS. A southern Union sympathiser wants to send word to his wife.
    - 11. 1864, Sept. 13.War Department, Ordnance Office. Printed, stamped Geo. T. Balch. Request for Return.
    - 12. 1864, Sept. 14.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 48. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Suspension of exchange of prisoners.
    - 13. 1864, Sept. 14.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 49. Printed. General court martial at Morganzia.
    - 14. 1864, Sept. 15.E. T. Burr to FS. ALS. Wishes a hearing or to be released from parole.
    - 15. 1864, Sept. 15.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 50. Proceedings of Council of War at New Orleans.
    - 16. 1864, Sept. 15.Division of West Mississippi - Office Assistant Inspector General. Printed circular No. 4.
    - 17. 1864, Sept. 15.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 257. Printed. Commercial intercourse between loyal and insurrectionary States.
    - 18. 1864, Sept. 16.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Price and Shelby.
    - 19. 1864, Sept. 16.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Mower expedition to start immediately.
    - 20. 1864, Sept. 17.Mrs. M. E. Bruce to FS. ALS. Personal thanks, requests eatables.
    - 21. 1864, Sept. 17.Geo. A. Mitchell to FS. ALS. Record of payments made to FS.
    - 22. 1864, Sept. 17.FS to A. J. Mower. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Sending guides, suggests ways of crossing rivers.
    - 23. 1864, Sept. 19.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 68. Printed. General court martial.
    - 24. 1864, Sept. 19.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 69. Printed. s. John F. Lacey. Lines of occupation defined contraband.
    - 25. 1864, Sept. 19.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 258. Printed. Fines imposed by military courts.
    - 26. 1864, Sept. 20.L. E. Barber and E. W. Crowl to FS. ANS. Invitation to lunch at Treasury Rooms.
    - 27. 1864, Sept. 20.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 51. Printed. Products of insurrectionary districts coming from beyond lines of occupation.
    - 28. 1864, Sept. 20.John J. Peck. Siege of Suffolk--Chancellorsville. Printed broadside.
  - Correspondence 1864, September 21-30. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1. 1864, Sept. 21.Geo. A. Mitchell to [FS]. ALS. Shifting seat buggy, horses, payment of army in Arkansas.
    - 2. 1864, Sept. 21.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 259. Printed. Sheridan to command Middle Military Division.
    - 3. 1864, Sept. 21.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 260. Bills for job printing.
    - 4. 1864, Sept. 22.Thomas O'Reilly to [FS]. ALS. Mr. Hirsch, a dangerous enemy.
    - 5. 1864, Sept. 22.FS to Mrs. Bruce. ALS. Flattering refusal.
    - 6. 1864, Sept. 22.FS to J. J. Raynolds. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Rebels from Texas to attack Ft. Smith.
    - 7. 1864, Sept. 22.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 75. Regulations for volunteer officers.
    - 8. 1864, Sept. 22.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 261. Printed. Exchanged prisoners.
    - 9. 1864, Sept. 23.Theo[bald] Hartmann to FS. ALS. Muster out of members of 13th Illinois Cavalry Volunteers.
    - 10. 1864, Sept. 23.FS to J. J. Reynolds. Copy s. W. D. Green. Texas troops.
    - 11. 1864, Sept. 23.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 262. Printed. Travel permits for officers of benevolent associations, etc.
    - 12. 1864, Sept. 24.Division of West Mississippi - Office Chief of Cavalry. Printed circular No. 5. Cavalry duty, use of cavalry.
    - 13. 1864, Sept. 26.M. M. Hayden to FS. ALS. Re: a published letter of Lt. Hosford.
    - 14. 1864, Sept. 26.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Enemy movements in Arkansas.
    - 15. 1864, Sept. 26.John B. Steele to FS. ALS. FS has been attacked in newspapers, politics.
    - 16. 1864, Sept. 27.Stephen Miller [Governor of Minnesota] to FS. ALS. Wants of 3rd Minnesota Volunteers.
    - 17. 1864, Sept. 28.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 52. Printed.
    - 18. 1864, Sept. 28.W. D. Green to J. G. Haskell. Official copy s. Green. Relieve all enlisted cavalry on detached service.
    - 19. 1864, Sept. 28.W. D. Green to J. H. Pratt. Official copy s. Green. Same as #18.
    - 20. 1864, Sept. 28.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 263. Printed. Hooker to command Northern Dept.
    - 21. 1864, Sept. 30.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 53. Printed. Court martial.
    - 22. 1864, Sept. 30.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 54. Printed. Court martial of Lt. Col. Chas. E. Clark.
    - 23. 1864, Sept. 30.John F. Lacey to FS. ALS. Re: Price, Sheridan's victory, price of gold down.
    - 24. 1864, Sept. 30.Geo. O. Sokalski to [FS]. ALS. Information re: Price's movements.
    - 25. 1864, Sept. 30.[FS] to Powell Clayton. Copy tel., fragment. Sending reinforcements to Pine Bluff.
  - Correspondence 1864, October 1-10. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 1. 1864, Oct. 1.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 79. Changes of commissaries and assistant commissaries.
    - 2. 1864, Oct. 1.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 264. Printed. Printing bills.
    - 3. 1864, Oct. 1.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 265. Printed. Distribution of election tickets and proxies in the Army.
    - 4. 1864, Oct. 3.Dept. of Arkansas. G.O. No. 70. Printed. 100 gun salute for Sheridan's victory.
    - 5. 1864, Oct. 3.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 55. Printed. Military commission.
    - 6. 1864, Oct. 3.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 56. Printed. Acting ordnance officers.
    - 7. 1864, Oct. 3.FS to Powell Clayton. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Sending cavalry brigade.
    - 8. 1864, Oct. 4.J. D. O'Connell to FS. ALS. Wants promotion.
    - 9. 1864, Oct. 4.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Magruder against Pine Bluff, etc.
    - 10. 1864, Oct. 4.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 266. Printed Clothing allowance.
    - 11. 1864, Oct. 4.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 267. Printed. Exchanged prisoners.
    - 12. 1864, Oct. 5.S. C. Benham to FS. ADS. Mess bill and cover.
    - 13. 1864, Oct. 5.W. S. Rosecrans to FS. LS. Movements of enemy, Pilot's Knob.
    - 14. 1864, Oct. 5.John M. Thayer to [FS]. ALS. Situation at Ft. Smith, enemy movements, Blunt.
    - 15. 1864, Oct. 6.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 285. Printed. Aid to Treasury Dept. officers and agents.
    - 16a. 1864, Oct. 7.Alfred Brown to FS. ALS. Appeal.
    - 16b. 1864, Oct. 7.S. H. Tucker to FS. ALS. Appeal.
    - 17-19. 1864, Oct. 8.C. T. Christensen to F. J. Herron. 3 copies, one s. Wm. Hyde Clarke, two s. Chas. T. Scammon. Orders on inspection of irregularities in Dept. of Arkansas: fraud in supply depts. of Ft. Smith, etc.
    - 20. 1864, Oct. 8.C. T. Christensen to FS. ALS. Re: inspection tour by Herron.
    - 21. 1864, Oct. 8.Division of West Mississippi. Printed circular No. 7. Re: provision returns.
    - 22. 1864, Oct. 8.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 57. Printed. Re: H. R. Putnam.
    - 23. 1864, Oct. 8.Unknown [Clara] to Dear Sister. ALS. Louisville, Ky., school and family.
    - 24. 1864, Oct. 9.Edw. B. Hubbard to FS. ALS. Return to service, rank.
    - 25. 1864, Oct. 9.FS to E. R. S. Canby. Copy tel. s. W. D. Green. Enemy withdrawal.
    - 26. 1864, Oct. 10.C. C. Andrews to FS. ALS. Duvalls Bluff, wants more men.
    - 27. 1864, Oct. 10.[Joseph H. Brown] to Dear Relatives. A True Copy of a letter captured by a scout of this dept. s. L. B. Nash. Re: Confederates in Arkansas.
    - 28. 1864, Oct. 10.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 268. Printed. Re-enlistment.
  - Correspondence 1864, October 11-20. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 1. 1864, Oct. 11.J. W. Davidson to FS. LS. Recalling detached cavalrymen.
    - 2. 1864, Oct. 11.Division of West Mississippi. Printed circular No. 8. Re: Lt. Col. Samuel Hamblen, 10th Regiment U. S. Heavy Artillery (colored).
    - 3. 1864, Oct. 11.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 58. Printed. Reprint of a letter of Henry W. Allen to J. A. Seddon recommending use of negroes as soldiers in Confederate Army.
    - 4. 1864, Oct. 11.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 59. Printed. Recapture of regimental flags.
    - 5. 1864, Oct. 11.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 60. Printed. Fines.
    - 6. 1864, Oct. 11.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 61. Printed. Detention of steamboats.
    - 7. 1864, Oct. 11.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 269. Printed. Money and property taken from political prisoners and prisoners of war.
    - 8. 1864, Oct. 11.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 270. Printed. Duties of Bureau of Military Justice.
    - 9. 1864, Oct. 13.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 62. Printed. Keily court martial.